Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5, Section 1: Boxes 1-22 1870-2017
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
- Mitre Corporation, Publication (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Item 3: Mobile Chemical Company, Publication (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Item 4: Facts About Mobil Corporation, Publication (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Item 5: Mobil: Corporate Policy Statements, Publication (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Item 6: EEO at Mobile: Partnership in Progress, Publication (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Item 7: "Made Possible by a grant from Mobil" A Guide to Mobil's Support of Arts and Culture, Publication (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Item 8: Facts about Mobil Corporation, Publication (Box 20, Folder 30)
    Full year, 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Mobil World Vol. 57, No. 3: Special Issue, Publication (Box 20, Folder 30)
    March 1991. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Mobil at 125, Publication (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Item 11: A Brief History of Mobil, Publication (Box 20, Folder 30)
- Mobil Oil Corporation - Handbooks, manuals, etc., Publication (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Chronological Fact Sheet, Publication (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Item 2: Foreward: A publication for Montgomery Ward people, Publication (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Item 3: Forecast of Potential, Publication (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Item 4: Appraisal of Performance, Publication (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Item 5: Correspondence Concerning Objective Setting and Appraisal Program Supplement, Publication (Box 20, Folder 31)
    January 14, 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Correspondence Concerning Guidelines for the Objective Setting and Appraisal Program, Publication (Box 20, Folder 31)
    January 7, 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Objectives/Action Plan Record Sheet, Publication (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Item 8: Montgomery Ward & Co. The End of "Caveat Emptor", Publication (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Item 9: Montgomery Ward: The End of "Caveat Emptor", Publication (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Item 10: Montgomery Ward Facts: Chronological Fact Sheet, Publication (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Item 11: Montgomery Ward News Service: Reaching New Goals, Publication (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Item 12: Montgomery Ward: Leadership in Retailing, Publication (Box 20, Folder 31)
- Montgomery Ward & Company - Handbooks, manuals, etc., Publication (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Monsanto, Publication (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Item 2: Your Future and Monsanto, Publication (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Item 3: The New World of Monsanto, Publication (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Item 4: Helping create the employe climatea contribution you can make a a Personnel Professional at Monsanto, Publication (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Item 5: Your Future and Monsanto, Publication (Box 20, Folder 32)
- Monsanto - Handbooks, manuals, etc., Publication (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Products and Services: For Every Business Recordkeeping Requirement, Publication (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Item 2: First Day Checklist--Administration, Publication (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Item 3: Employee Progress Appraisal Form, Publication (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Item 4: A Career with Moorethe Sky is the Limit, Publication (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Item 5: Moore and YouA Bright Future Together!, Publication (Box 20, Folder 33)
- Moore Business Forms, Inc. - Handbooks, manuals, etc., Publication (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: The Morgan Guaranty Survey, Publication (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Item 2: The Morgan Guaranty Survey, Publication (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Item 3: The Morgan Guaranty Survey, Publication (Box 20, Folder 34)
- Morgan Guaranty Trust Company, Publication (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Morton F. Plant Hospital Program, Publication (Box 20, Folder 35)
- Morton F. Plant Hospital, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Saving Energy! Motor Vehicle Manufacturers Meet the Challenge with New ProductsNew Systems, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Item 2: Consumer Advisory: Methaol-Gasoline Blends Can Cause Serious Problems to Motor Vehivles, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Item 3: MVMA, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Item 4: Career Opportunities in Automotive Service, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Item 5: Robotic Safety Conference, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
    June 1-2, 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: A New Dawn for the Transportation Industry, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
    April 8, 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: "Introduction to MORT Techniques" A Workshop on Systems Safety, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
    March 26-27 or March 28-29, 1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Your Way to Better Fuel Economy, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
    June, 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Directory of Motor Vehicle Related Associations, 1981 Edition, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Item 10: Motor Vehicles Manufacturers Association: What it is, What it Does, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Item 11: Sound & Noise, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Item 12: America Runs on Wheels: The National Scope of the Motor Vehicle Industry, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Item 13: MVMA News Release for Immediate Release, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Item 14: How to Save Truck Fuel, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
    October, 1982 Edition. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: The Truck & Bus Manufacturing Industry: Building the Tools That Move America, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Item 16: Heavy Truck Safetythe Need to Know, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Item 17: Remarks by V. J. Adduci, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
    By V. J. Adduci. October 26, 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Remarks by V. J. Adduci, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
    By V. J. Adduci. October 20-22, 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Remarks by Thomas F. Longerbeam, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
    By Thomas F. Longerbeam. October 13, 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Remarks by V. J. Adduci, Annual Meeting, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
    By V. J. Adduci. October 3, 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Remarks by Lawrence E. Slimak, 32nd Annual Conference, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
    By Lawrence E. Slimak. September 27, 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Dr. Fred W. Bowditch before The Society of the Plastics Industry of Canada, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
    By Dr. Fred W. Bowditch. September 27, 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: The Automobile Engine and Alternate Fuels, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
    By Harry B. Weaver. September 15, 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Statement of Motor Vehicle Manufacturers Association of the United States, Inc., Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
    By Dr. Fred W. Bowditch. November, 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Remarks by Lawrence Slimak: The 1990 Vehicle, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
    By Lawrence Slimak. November 15, 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Remarks by V. J. Adduci, 24th Annual Convention: Hawaii Automobile Dealers Association, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
    By V. J. Adduci. November 18, 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Remarks by V. J. Adduci: National Hghway Safety Symposium, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
    By V. J. Adduci. February 28, 29 and March 1, 1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: MVMA News Release, Collection of News Releases, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Item 29: MVMA News Release, Collection of News Releases, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Item 30: Robotic Safety Presented at the National Safety Congress, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
    October 19, 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: MVMA 1984 Motor Vehicle Information, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
- Motor Vehicle Manufacturers Association - Handbooks, manuals, etc., Publication (Box 20, Folder 37)
- Mt. Sinai Occupational Medicine Clinic - We Care to Work, Not to Die: A Conference for People of Color and Low Wage Workers on How to Improve Safety and Health at Our Workplaces, February 23, 1991, Publication (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: We came to Work Not to Die: A Conference for People of Color and Low Wage Workers on How to Improve Safety and Health at Our Workplaces, Publication (Box 21, Folder 1)
    By Mount Sinai Occupational Medicine Clinic. February 23, 1991. Item is in English.
- Nabisco Inc. "Employee Benefits", 1982; Publication (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Empliyee Benefits, Publication (Box 21, Folder 2)
    By NABISCO Inc. Item is in English.
- Nabisco - Handbooks, manuals, etc., Publication (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: NABISCO Inc., Publication (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Fact Sheet, Publication (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: About NFG, Publication (Box 21, Folder 3)
    By NABISCO Inc. March 1992. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Collective Bargaining Agreements, Publication (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Personnel Management Development Program, Publication (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: College Relations: Newsletter Vol. 1 No. 1, Publication (Box 21, Folder 3)
    By NABISCO Inc. Fall 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: NBI Today Vol. 8 No. 7, Publication (Box 21, Folder 3)
    By NABISCO Inc. July 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: NBI Today Vol. 5 No. 11, Publication (Box 21, Folder 3)
    By NABISCO Inc. November 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: 42 Million a Day: The Story of Nabisco Brands, Publication (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: Drug-Free Workplace Statement of Policy, Publication (Box 21, Folder 3)
    By NABISCO Inc. June 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: A New Way of life!, Publication (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: Salaried Retiree Benefits Plans, Publication (Box 21, Folder 3)
- National Academy of Arbitrators - Handbooks, Manuals, etc., Publication (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Union Busting, Inc, Publication (Box 21, Folder 4)
    By National Academy of Management Development. Item is in English.
- National Academy of Management Development, Publication (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: National Alliance of Business Folder, Publication (Box 21, Folder 5)
    By National Alliance of Business. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Dislocated Worker: There are Answers, Publication (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Economic Development and Job Creation, Publication (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Business Currents Technical Report: No. 10, Publication (Box 21, Folder 5)
    By National Alliance of Business. July 13, 1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Corporate Action Agenda: The Business of Improving Public Education, Publication (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: National Alliance of Business: News Release, Publication (Box 21, Folder 5)
    By National Alliance of Business. June 11, 1990. Item is in English.
  - Publication (Box 21, Folder 5)
- National Alliance of Business, Publication (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The Labor Department: Its Policies, Guidelines and Goals as Mandated by the Board of Directors, Publication (Box 21, Folder 6)
    By NAACP. June 1985. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Primer on Affirmative Action, Publication (Box 21, Folder 6)
    By NAACP. Item is in English.
- NAACP, Publication (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: National Association of Aluminum Distributors: progress through service, Publication (Box 21, Folder 7)
    By National Associaion of Aluminum Distributors. Item is in English.
- Nat'l. Assoc. of Aluminum Distributors, Publication (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Factbook for Employers, Publication (Box 21, Folder 8)
    By National Association of Employers on Health Care Alternatives. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Checklist for Employers: Employer Evaluation Guide another service of, Publication (Box 21, Folder 8)
- National Association of Employers on Health Care Alternatives, Publication (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Publication (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: A House Policy for the 1980s: 1981 Statement of Policy, Publication (Box 21, Folder 9)
    By National Association of Home Builders. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Restrict Money Market Funds Builders Tell Congress, Publication (Box 21, Folder 9)
    By National Association of Home Builders. May 14, 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: NAHB Builder: The Voice of America's Housing Industry Vol. 4, Publication (Box 21, Folder 9)
    By National Association of Home Builders. April 20, 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Ease Restrictions on Lumber Shipments Builders Ask Congress, Publication (Box 21, Folder 9)
    By National Association of Home Builders. 6/23/81. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Home Builder Ask Congress for VA Graduated Payment Mortgage, Publication (Box 21, Folder 9)
    By National Association of Home Builders. 6/10/81. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Savings Certificates Called Landmark Tax Legislation by NAHB, Publication (Box 21, Folder 9)
    By National Association of Home Builders. July 17, 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Strong FHA Program Still Needed, Builder Says, Publication (Box 21, Folder 9)
    By National Association of Home Builders. 4/14/81. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Housing Recovery Not Seen Before 1982, Economists Say, Publication (Box 21, Folder 9)
    By National Association of Home Builders. 4/22/81. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: NAHB Board of Directors to meet in Washington, Publication (Box 21, Folder 9)
    By National Association of Home Builders. 4/29/81. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Housing at the Turning Point, Publication (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Item 12: Housing Background, Publication (Box 21, Folder 9)
    By National Association of Home Builders. July 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Interest Rate Hikes Abort Chances for Economic Recovery, Publication (Box 21, Folder 9)
    By National Association of Home Builders. 5/5/81. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: NAHB Board Calls for Tax Incentives for Savers, Publication (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Item 15: Tax Free Savings Endorsed by Home Builders, Publication (Box 21, Folder 9)
    By National Association of Home Builders. 5/18/81. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Journalism Competition Announced by NAHB, Publication (Box 21, Folder 9)
    By National Association of Home Builders. 5/21/81. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Home Builders to Take Convention To Atlanta, Publication (Box 21, Folder 9)
    By National Association of Home Builders. 5/26/81. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Tax Credit Could Stimulate Passive Solar Market, Builders Say, Publication (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Item 19: Presidential Housing Commission Applauded by Home Builders, Publication (Box 21, Folder 9)
    By National Association of Home Builders. 6/17/1981. Item is in English.
- Nat'l. Assoc. of Home Builders, Publication (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Industry's Agenda for the 97th Congress, Publication (Box 21, Folder 10)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Some Dos and Don'ts for Supervisors, Publication (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: A fedeal Program Run Aground: The Longshoremen's & Harbor Workers' Compensation Act, Publication (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: Minimum Universal Pension System, Publication (Box 21, Folder 10)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. October 21, 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Statement Submitted by the National Association of Manufacturers for the Pension Task Force Subcommittee on Labor Management Relations House Committee on Education and Labor on Title I of H.R. 6525: The Public Employee Retirement Income Security Act of 19, Publication (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: Letter to Honorable Dan Quayle, Chairman Subcommittee on Employment and Productivity Senate Committee on Labor and Human Resources, Publication (Box 21, Folder 10)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. July 2, 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Summary of the National Association of Manufacturers' Testimony on the Administration's Proposed Savings on Unemployment Compensation before the Ways and Means Committee, Publication (Box 21, Folder 10)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. March 11, 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Letter to Honorable Robert W. Kasten, Jr. Chairman, Publication (Box 21, Folder 10)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. May 1, 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Letter to Messieurs Edward H. O'Connell, Jr., Publication (Box 21, Folder 10)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. October 27, 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Summary of The National Association of Manufacturers' Testimony on Proposed Savings on Trade Adjustment Assistance Unemployment Compensation before the Subcommittee on Trade Ways and Means Committee, Publication (Box 21, Folder 10)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. March 31, 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Statement of Irvine H. Dearnley, Vice President, Citibank, NA on behalf of the National Association of Manufacturers on the Final Report of the President's Commission on Pension Policy before the Subcommittee on Savings, pensions, and Investment Policy Co, Publication (Box 21, Folder 10)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. May 15, 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Testimony of Irvine Dearnley, representing the National Association of Manufacturers Before the President's Commission on Pension Policy on Universal Social Security Coverage, Publication (Box 21, Folder 10)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. April 18, 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Proposed Section 441(d)1 Regulations, Publication (Box 21, Folder 10)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. June 9, 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Proposed Section 411(d)(1) Regulations, Publication (Box 21, Folder 10)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. August 11, 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: The Risk Retention Act: HR 2120 Representative Florio, Publication (Box 21, Folder 10)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. July 17, 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Davis-BaconSending Federal Construction Costs out of Sight, Publication (Box 21, Folder 10)
- National Association of Manufacturers - Handbooks, manuals, etc., Publication (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: NAPF News Vol. 6 No. 1, Publication (Box 21, Folder 11)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. April 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: 1981 Membership Directory, Publication (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Publications Available from the NAPF, Publication (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Publication (Box 21, Folder 11)
- National Association of Plastic Fabricators, Publication (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: The Printing Ink Industry and NAPIM, Publication (Box 21, Folder 12)
    By National Association of Printers and Lithographers. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Forward, Publication (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: Publications of the National Association of Printing Ink Manufacturers, Publication (Box 21, Folder 12)
- National Association of Printers and Lithographers, Publication (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Management's Toughest Challenge: Motivating Your People, Publication (Box 21, Folder 13)
    By National Association of Printers & Lithographers. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: CA137: People-Press Manning, Training, Retraining, Publication (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: CA 247: Management's Toughest Challenge: Motivating Your People, Publication (Box 21, Folder 13)
- National Association of Printers & Lithographers, Publication (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: NASDAQ Glossary Series, Publication (Box 21, Folder 14)
    By National Association of Securities Dealers. March 1, 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The NASDAQ Glossary Series, Publication (Box 21, Folder 14)
    By National Association of Securities Dealers. April2, 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The NASDAQ Glossary Series, Publication (Box 21, Folder 14)
    By National Association of Securities Dealers. May 3, 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: NASD Guide to Information and Services, Publication (Box 21, Folder 14)
    By National Association of Securities Dealers. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: An Introduction to the NASD, Publication (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Item 6: Three Outlooks on Underwriting Vol. XXXXI Nos. 1 & 2, Publication (Box 21, Folder 14)
    By National Association of Securities Dealers. July 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: NASDAQ Vol. 6 No. 1, Publication (Box 21, Folder 14)
    By National Association of Securities Dealers. April 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: NASDAW Vol. 2 No. 7, Publication (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Item 9: Reprint of the Manual May 1981, Publication (Box 21, Folder 14)
    By mgtcirc@cornell.edu. May 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Private Offerings of Direct Participation Programs, Publication (Box 21, Folder 14)
    By National Association of Securities Dealers. April 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: NASDAQ and The Listing Dilemma: Factors to be Considered by OTC Companies Contemplating Stock Exchange Listing, Publication (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Item 12: Corporate Responsibility: Choices and Challenges for Management, Publication (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Item 13: How Porgressive NASDAQ Companies Attract Investors: How Market Makers Select Their Favorite NASDAQ Securities, Publication (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Item 14: How to Become a Member of the NASD, Publication (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Nat'l. Assoc. of Securities Dealers, Publication (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: NASS News/ Views: National Association of Suggestion Systems, Publication (Box 21, Folder 15)
    By National Association of Suggestion Systems House Organs. March/ April 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: President's Report, Publication (Box 21, Folder 15)
    By National Association of Suggestion Systems House Organs. Item is in English.
- National Assoc. of Suggestion Systems - House Organs, Publication (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Membership Information, Publication (Box 21, Folder 16)
    By National Association of Suggestion Systems. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Key to Your Success Is People, Publication (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: 41st Annual Inernational Conference, Publication (Box 21, Folder 16)
    By National Association of Suggestion Systems. October 5-8, 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Key Program for Maximum Suggestion System Results, Publication (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Item 5: Legal Guidelines, Publication (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Item 6: Purposes and Aims, Publication (Box 21, Folder 16)
    By National Association of Suggestion Systems. March-April Issue. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Enrichment Session, Publication (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Item 8: Answering to your Questions, Publication (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Item 9: All Rise and Publicize, Publication (Box 21, Folder 16)
    By ENGL 2800. Third Quarter 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: 1982 NASS Board of Directors, Publication (Box 21, Folder 16)
    By ENGL 2800. January/ February 1982. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Vitamin R (Recognition) Have you Had yours Today?, Publication (Box 21, Folder 16)
    By Susan E. Anderson. Item is in English.
- National Association of Suggestion Systems, Publication (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Temporary Help, Publication (Box 21, Folder 17)
    By National Association of Temporary Services. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Discover the advantage...Freedom Flexibility Choice Controlwith a career in Temporary Help Services, Publication (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: Make More of Your Great American Retirement Dream, Publication (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Item 4: Lexicon of Terms, Publication (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Item 5: Temporary Help Meets Businesses' Changing Demands, Publication (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Item 6: How to buy temporary help services, Publication (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Item 7: Temporary Jobs: Making Them Work for You, Publication (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Item 8: "Issues and Answers", Publication (Box 21, Folder 17)